认识我的人都知道
Anyone who knows me will tell you
-我很喜欢表达爱意  -别摸了
- I'm an affectionate guy. - Stop it. Stop it. Stop.
我常把“我爱老婆”挂在嘴边
I love my wife. I say it all the time.
有时候
And sure,
她确实会没那个心情 不过
sometimes she's not in the mood, but...
我能让她欲火焚身
I warm her up.
相信我
Believe me,
开始做的时候 她就快活似神仙了
she's happy once we get going.
我做了我该做的
I do my part.
-做好了  -嘿
- Okay. - Hey!
我只是想让她做她该做的
All I'm asking is that she does hers.
周五
- Oh. - Friday.
-亲爱的 今天不行  -嘿
- Not today, honey. - Hey.
婚礼宣誓是时候可是说好了的
It's right there in the wedding vows...
-不要  -嘿
- No. - Hey.
爱 尊重和服从
Love, honor, and obey.
我说了我想要辣的
I said I want 'em spicy.
满足我很难吗
How hard is it to give me what I want?
抱歉亲爱的 我知道你喜欢辣的
Sorry, sweetheart. I know you like it hot.
-没错  -行吗
- Hey. - Yeah?
这才对嘛
That's what I'm talking about.
爽啊
Oh, yeah.
爽死了
Fuck yeah.
妈的 宝贝
Oh, damn, babe.
就是这样
Yup. Yup.
辣死我了
God, it burns!
天哪
Ow! God!
我遇上了你
你好
Hi. Hello.
我是不是 是这啊
Am I-- yeah, I am here.
我明白了 天哪
Oh. Oh, my God.
尽管震惊吧
Okay, let it out.
这样多久了
How Iong has this been going on?
你知道吗 算了
You know what? Yeah, no. You know what?
我不该管这事
That's really none of my business at all.
除非你需要我帮忙 那就眨两次眼
Unless blink twice if you need help.
看看啊
Oh, well, well, well.
这是谁从纽约回来了呀
Look who's back from the Big Apple.
我不知道你的语气为什么
Yeah, I don't know why you're saying that
得意洋洋的
so triumphantly.
我住这呢
I live here.
进来吧 我在做煎饼呢
Come on in. I'm making flapjacks.
还是不了
No. That-- nope.
我就站这和你说吧
I'll just talk to you right here.
等你尝了这松软的煎饼
Oh, once you get a taste of these fluffies,
就会改口了
you'll be singing a different tune.
你对这鸟没什么意见么
So you're okay with the bird?
我见过比这装的更大的逼
It's not my favorite affectation.
不管你来是想说什么 我们都没事了
Whatever you came here to say, we're good.
争吵 过激是很正常的事
People fight. Emotions run high.
我很佩服你
I gotta give you credit.
下了很大决心才来的吧 带着诚意
It takes a lot to come here, you know, hat in hand.
我不是来道歉的
No, I'm not here to apologize.
我看到比利的那些照片了
I saw the pictures of Billy.
你不能发表那些照片 你知道的
You cannot publish those, and you know it.
那些照片违背了
They are a betrayal
我们共同建立的一切
of everything we've been building together.
如果你想在这件事上有发言权
Look, if you wanted a say in that shoot,
你当时怎么不来
then you should have been here for it.
道格 没有哪个正常的女人
Doug, no woman in her right mind
会同意这些的
is gonna sign off on those.
要不你问问你的新主编
Well, why don't we ask your new managing editor,
看看她怎么想
see what she thinks?
-蒂娜  -道格
- Tins? - Doug.
怎么了
What?
我也想咨询你意见的 但你辞职了
Look, I would've consulted with you, but you quit.
记得吗
You remember?
真是恭喜你啊
Wow. Congratulations.
你连代替我的人都找好了啊
You already found a replacement for me as well.
道格 你们不能这么做
Doug, you cannot do that.
我们当然能
Oh, yeah, we can.
这个周日可真忙啊
Busy Sunday at Casa Renetti.
看看是谁吧
Let's see who it is.
没事
It's okay.
替你高兴
Happy for you.
还没定下来呢
Deal's not final yet.
他妈的 我们是怎么惹上这事的
Ah, son of a bitch. We're on the hook for this how?
威尔克森夫妇全面开战
麻辣官司使社会巨星陨落
你们俩 还有那本
You two, along with the entity
《风骚女子》杂志
known as "Minx" magazine,
被原告威廉·威尔克森起诉
are being sued by plaintiff William Wilkerson,
他说你那篇关于婚内强奸的文章
who claims that your article about marital rape
煽动了他以前理智又可人的妻子
incited his formerly sane and loving wife
史高维尔是标示辣度的单位
用超过一百万史高维尔的辣度的物质
into maiming his penis with a substance measuring
使他的阴茎致残
over 1 million Scoville Units,
导致他的包皮受损
resulting in damage to the foreskin
阴茎体严重起泡
and audacious blistering of the shaft.
阴茎体严重起泡 不错啊
"Audacious blistering of the shaft," that's good.
人们都说太阳之下皆旧闻
And they say there's nothing new under the sun.
这个标题适合你的马戏团结尾
Fitting end to your circus:
我们被加农炮狠狠的射出
us being shot out of a cannon.
不得不承认 这是个绝佳的宣传噱头啊
Gotta admit, A-plus publicity stunt.
老威利真是有把柠檬变柠檬水的能耐
Good old Willy turning lemons into lemonade
或者把辣椒变成
or hot peppers into--
萨尔萨辣酱或者果酱什么的
Salsa or potentially jelly.
好了 干嘛呢
Okay, hello.
你们俩对待这件事可真严肃啊
I see you're taking this as seriously as he is.
布比 在这个行业 你要是没有娱乐精神
Bubbe, in this business, if you don't laugh,
就坚持不了多久
you don't last very long.
是啊 我和迈伦从露出膝盖还是犯罪时
Yeah, Myron and I have been dealing with this crap
就跟这些破事打交道了
since it was a crime to show your kneecaps, right?
提个小建议
Offer a little settlement,
就让这件事过去吧 大家都高兴了
make this go away, and everybody is happy.
不不不 我们要大干一场 我们反诉
No, no, no, no, no. We go big. We countersue.
-道格儿  -什么 绝对不行
- Dougele. - What? Absolutely not.
这种送上门的宣传赔什么钱啊 这可是份大礼
You cannot pay for this kind of publicity. This is a gift.
源于《木马屠城记》，比喻在敌方营垒里埋下伏兵里应外合的活动
是啊 特洛伊木马也是个礼物
Oh, yeah, like the Trojan horse was a gift.
为什么我也被起诉了
Why am I even named in this suit anyway?
他是出版商
He's the publisher.
我当时只是一个无权无势的小员工
I'm just-- I was just a powerless employee.
没有任何编辑权
I don't have any editorial control.
这上面说
According to this,
你是“母权制觉醒”的始作俑者
you're the creator of "The Matriarchy Awakens,"
主宰了这本杂志的
the original iteration of this magazine
还有这篇冒犯性文章的发布
and the offending article herein.
是啊 但这本杂志已经面目全非到
Yeah, but I don't even recognize
我都快认不出了
my own magazine anymore.
法律可不这么认为
Well, the law doesn't see it that way,
你要为你的所有权负责
and you're liable by virtue of your proprietary rights.
我的律师让我
You know my lawyer asked me
不要在直播的时候讨论我的官司
not to discuss my case on the air.
看得出来 你挺听话的
And I see you heeding this advice.
是啊 真抱歉
Yeah, I'm sorry,
但像乔伊斯·普里格这样的女人
but women like Joyce Prigger,
像《风骚女子》这样的杂志
magazines like "Minx,"
他们得清楚他们不能再吃这种红利了
they need to know that the free ride is over.
没错 我是在利用法律的力量
Oh, yeah, I'm using the power of the law,
但我同时也掌握着更有力量的东西
but in my other hand, I hold something more powerful:
民心
people.
不只是民心 还有“男人站起来”
Not just people. Men Energized Now.
男人已振奋
我们呼吁所有的“男人站起来”去大闹
We are calling on all M.E.N. to get out there
让普里格和底袋钱不好过
and make things uncomfortable for Prigger and Bottom Dollar,
他们是我们的头号公敌和二号公敌
AKA public enemies number one and two.
我觉得这个组织的名字
I think it's really clever
起的真的很妙
how the name of the organization is M.E.N.
简写就是男人
but it also spells "men."
男人很聪明的
Men are smart.
你是在说那个组织
Are you talking about the organization
-还是所有男人  -两者都是
- or men in general? - Both.
天哪
Oh, my God.
所有权
Proprietary rights?
所以你也拥有《风骚女子》的一部分吗
So you own part of "Minx"?
是的 道格的律师是这么说的
Yeah, according to Doug's lawyer
有个傲慢加大洛杉矶分校的图书馆管理员也这么说
and one very snooty clerk at the UCLA Law Library.
你不会是想
Please tell me you're not trying to--
行使我的权利吗 我当然要
Exercise my rights? You bet I am.
你不会想引战的
You don't wanna go to war.
你只看到了道格善良的一面
You've only seen Doug's nice side.
-这就是他好的一面吗  -没错
- That's his nice side? - Mm-hmm.
去问问弗雷德·萨尔茨堡公司吧
Ask Fred Salzburg,
这么多年都收道格双倍钱的报纸商
the paper vendor who double-billed Doug for years.
怎么回事 弗雷德怎么了
Why? What happened to Fred?
没人知道 老爷子已经不在了
No one knows, but it's no longer called
现在叫萨尔茨堡家族公司了
Salzburg &Sons.
好吧 我为萨尔茨堡家的事感到遗憾
Okay, well, I'm very sorry for the Salzburg family,
但《风骚女子》是我们的孩子
but "Minx" is our baby.
我们不能置之不理
- Mm. - We can't just walk away.
-别说“我们”  -他这可是在扼杀我们的孩子啊
- Don't say "we." - But he's murdering our child.
我这个老父亲
Yeah, well, my paternal instincts
还没感受到呢
haven't kicked in just yet.
-换个理由吧  -好吧
- Try something else. - Fine.
没你我做不到
I can't do this without you.
我不想没有你单干 里奇
And I don't wanna do it without you, Richie.
你在各个方面都让杂志变得更好
You make the magazine better in every way,
我知道你明白这点的
and I know that you know this,
我也知道你和我一样在乎它
and I know that you care about it as much as I do.
来吧 里奇 我们该出场了
Come on, Richie. This is our time.
《风骚女子》是我们的孩子 我们不能
"Minx" is our baby. We can't--
我加入 我们去告诉道格吧
I'm in. Let's go tell Doug.
太好了 行
Oh, great. All right.
-你不穿鞋子吗  -大地就是我的鞋子
- Don't you need shoes? - The Earth is my shoe.
快走
Go. Go.
好吧
Okay, okay.
靠
Oh! Shit.
我们也有权利
We have rights too.
-男权  -够了
- Men rights. - Come on.
诺曼 你在干什么
Norman, what are you doing?
男人们终于开始反击了
Men are finally fighting back.
是吗 你要把威利老婆的事怪我们头上
Oh, yeah, you're blaming us for Willy's wife?
威利战争打响
女孩们
是斗不过
男人的
男人大于“风骚女人”
她是个疯子 诺曼 看看她嫁给了谁
She's a nut job, Norm. Look at who she married.
你站她那边吗 得了吧
You're siding with her now? Come on.
你怎么回事啊
What happened to you, man?
我谁的边都不站
I'm not siding with anyone.
你能挪个位置 让我开进去吗
Can you just move so I can get in my spot?
好吧
All right.
太好了
Oh, that's nice.
诺曼交了一些朋友
Norman made some friends.
在这个国家 每20秒
A woman is sexually assaulted
就有一名妇女遭到性侵犯
every 20 seconds in this country.
而一个男人的香肠被喝倒彩
One guy gets a boo-boo on his wiener,
就是世界末日了
and it's the end of the fucking world.
乔伊斯 这是你第一次骂人吗
Joyce, is that your first swear?
是啊 你说呢
Yeah, could you tell?
-说的怎么样  -很棒
- How was it? - It was great.
-会不会太  -说的很棒
- Was it-- - It was great.
很自然
Yeah. Mm-hmm. Natural.
我从没硬闯进过刚辞职的地方
I've never marched in someplace and just quit before.
我有过 因为发生了流血事件
I have. There was bloodshed.
大剌剌走进我的门
Oh, something tells me
看起来可不像什么道歉啊
this isn't an apology walking in my door.
不是的 先生
No, sir, it is not.
在所有权问题解决之前
Until issues of ownership have been resolved,
请你立即停止出版
please immediately cease and desist publication
第三期《风骚女子》
of the third issue of "Minx."
手写的
Handwritten.
为了彰显个人风度吗
For that personal touch?
我的打印机没墨了
My Selectric was out of ink.
你们两个笨蛋来干什么
And what are you two knuckleheads doing?
他们是和我一起的
They are with me.
谢谢你把你的意图
Well, thank you for informing me
通知给我 乔伊斯
of your intentions, Joyce.
我们接下来怎么办
What do we do? What do we do?
我们走吧 非常感谢
Let's go. Thank you.
如果你跑上了所有的垒
Well, if you touched all the bases,
在我看来 就是个本垒打
in my book, that's a home run.
你告诉罗杰·米德尔顿
You tell Roger Middleton that it doesn't matter
如果这是一个滚地球和三次失误也没事
if it was a ground ball and three errors.
也一样重要 天啊 他和他妈妈真像
It still counts. God, he's just like his mom.
哦 我真希望能看看
Oh, I wish I could have seen it.
不 没关系 你去吧
No, it's okay. Go. Yeah, go.
等我旅行回来之后
We'll talk more when I'm back from my--
我们再聊
my trip.
嗯嗯 我爱你
Okay, love you.
啊 我最爱的两个人
Oh, my two favorite people.
把徕卡相机拿走吧
Take the Leica.
只有你懂得欣赏它
You're the only one who really appreciates it.
谢谢 道格
Thanks, Doug.
-已经拿上了  -很好 你了解我
- Already did. - Oh, good. You know me.
就算我的人要走 我也要把他们照顾得棒棒的
I like to take care of my people even if they move on.
抱歉 我修改一下
Sorry, let me say that again.
就算他们背后捅了我一刀
Even if they stab me in the back
然后要走
and then move on.
我看到比利那张插页了
I saw that Billy centerfold.
你捅了自己一刀
You stabbed yourself.
只不过暂时坎坷而已
But you wanna throw away years of our relationship
你就把我们多年的合作抛在一边么
over a couple of bad days?
真觉得乔伊斯一个人
And do you really think Joyce has what it takes
能撑起这一切
to do all this on her own?
怎么说呢 道格
I don't know, Doug.
如果没有《风骚女子》 可能未来十年
If it wasn't for "Minx," you'd have me
你都会让我给别人拔阴毛
plucking stray pubes for the next decade.
那你再仔细想想
Right, cause if you think about it,
在她决定来为我们工作前
I had the idea for you to shoot for "Minx"
我就想让你当《风骚女子》的摄影师了
before she ever walked through those office doors.
所以你现在要单飞了吗
So, what, you're making moves now?
急于证明自己对吗
You're a hustler?
听我一句劝
Then let me give you a little advice.
我建议你留下来当个大明星
I recommend you stay here in the big leagues
而不是跟她一起去个名不见经传的地方
as opposed to shipping off to Palookaville with her.
你要真想留住我
Well, if you really want me,
就给我开个无法拒绝的职位吧
I suggest you make me an offer I can't refuse.
初步建议
Some initial suggestions.
增加两名编辑助理
Two editorial assistants.
很好 看来你出师了
Good. Taught you something.
你会的一切都是我教的
And I know I taught you everything.
我最讨厌冲突了
I hate conflict.
我胄里都尴尬翻江倒海了
My stomach feels like the butter churn at Spahn Ranch.
没错 是谁帮你收拾烂摊子的
Yeah, and who got you out of that mess?
你要是半夜打给乔伊斯
What, you think you're gonna call Joyce
她会把你偷偷藏在后备箱
and she's gonna smuggle you out
带你出去吗
in the trunk of her car at00 a.m.?
-不知道 也许吧  -她会喝杯牛奶
- I don't know, maybe. - She's gonna be asleep
睡得跟猪一样
with a glass of milk, out cold.
你的条件我考虑下 大帅哥
I'll take a look at these, hotshot.
你找到那个地址了吗
Did you find that address?
你确定要这么做吗
You sure about this?
当然不确定
Of course not.
这甜品真的很诱人
You're really tempting me,
但我必须得保持少女般的身材
but I do have to keep my girlish figure.
你肯定听说了吧 我又单身待嫁了
I'm back on the market, in case you hadn't heard.
能跟这样魅惑的女人约会 是每个男人的梦想 旺达
Well, any man would be lucky to date a fox like you, Wanda.
好了好了
Oh, well.
最近没多少人约我
My dance card's not exactly full these days.
男人觉得我太吓人了
I'm told that men find me intimidating.
我能懂
Yeah, well, I understand that.
都是因为媒体对你百般攻击
I think that's because you're taking a beating in the press,
我可以帮你扭转局面
and I can help turn that around for you.
威利的平台很大 受众很多
You know, Willy has a big platform
他也更敢说 这你肯定知道
and an even bigger mouth, which I think you know.
是啊
Yeah.
我觉得你也应该被大家倾听
- But I think you also deserve to be heard.
我自己就平台 这里专门塑造冠军女性
And I've got a venue that is built to champion women.
我从来没觉得自己是公众人物
I've never really thought of myself as a public figure.
贝齐·罗斯在帮丈夫缝裤子时
Betsy Ross was just sewing her husband's pants
发明了美国国旗
when she invented the American flag.
你知道吗
Did you know that?
罗莎·帕克斯在拒绝下车之后
Was Rosa Parks even an activist
才成一名平权活动家
before she refused to get off that bus?
你是说拒绝换座位吧
You mean refused to change seats?
乔伊斯·普里格
Joyce Prigger?
我能进来吗
- May I?
当然可以 请进
Of course. Yes, come in.
-谢谢  -乔伊斯·普里格竟然来我家了
- Thank you. - It's Joyce Prigger.
你好 旺达
- Wow. - Hello, Wanda.
你好你好 欢迎
- Hello. Welcome. - Hello.
乔伊斯 你在跟踪我吗
- What are you doing, tailing me now, Joyce?
没有 我是闻着操纵气味过来的
- Nope, just followed the smell of manipulation.
-真好  -旺达
- Great. - Wanda?
这个人不可信
- Hmm? - Do not trust this man
不要跟他合作
with your story.
他不在乎你
He does not care about you
不在乎我 不在乎任何人 真的
or me or anyone, really.
你俩是一对儿吗
- Oh, are you two an item?
呃 天哪 绝对不是
- Ew. God, no. - Oh, no.
我读出了被爱人抛弃的怨念
I'm just getting some jilted lover vibes.
作为一个商业伙伴来说 他确实伤了我的心
He did break my heart but as a business partner.
在全世界都没人理你时
- I promised you a magazine
我帮你办了杂志
when no one else in the world would.
然后转身把它交到
Only to turn around and then hand it over
那个江湖骗子温蒂·马手里
to that charlatan, Wendy Mah.
我喜欢《暴力性爱》
Oh, I love Aphrodisia.
你怎么知道温蒂的事的
Who told you about Wendy?
我底袋钱有朋友
I have friends at Bottom Dollar.
你敢这么说吗
Can you say the same thing?
我就是底袋钱
I am Bottom Dollar.
我就是《风骚女子》
And I am "Minx."
我会把这个女人
And I will save both my magazine
和我的杂志从你的掠夺中拯救出来
and this poor woman from your predatory ways.
可我不需要拯救
- I don't think I need saving.
对 因为你是个坚强独立好女人
No, because you are a strong, independent person.
好吧 我
- Okay, I--
别让他继续散播
- Don't let him perpetuate
这可怕的谎言了
this disgusting lie that's already out there.
你肯定不是读了我的文章 才去报复你老公对
My article obviously did not inspire your act of revenge.
其实就是
Oh, it did, actually.
那么 旺达
- Well, come on, Wanda. That's--
听着 威利从没强迫过我
Listen, Willy never forced me,
不像你写的那些女人
not like the women that you wrote about.
但是 你说一个妻子没心情就可以
But I mean, you show me a wife who's never had sex
不用做爱 我会说你要么是骗子
when she's not in the mood, and I'll show you a liar
要么你们的婚姻还在蜜月期
or at the very least, a woman who's still on her honeymoon.
这篇文章真的让我思考
So it did-- the article, it got me thinking.
但我没建议你诉诸暴力
- But I didn't suggest turning to violence.
我没想到会造成那么大的伤害
well, I didn't know that it was gonna do that much damage.
我还以为
I thought it would just,
会让他辣辣的 最后很刺激呢
you know, burn a little bit and be funny.
真是太有趣了
- And it was very funny.
我不想忽视这事的悲剧色彩
Not to take away from any of your suffering,
但用墨西哥辣椒打手枪还挺
but the jalapeno hand job was very--
-我们正说着话呢  -本来是我跟她在说话
- We're talking here. - No, we were actually talking.
你横插一脚
- We're talking. You're making it worse.
-你明白吗  -能让我说完吗
- Do you understand-- - Can I finish?
-对不起  -请讲
- Sorry. - Please.
我只是受够了在自己家
I just got sick of being told what to do
被人呼来喝去的感觉了
and who to be in my own home.
有些人只是想利用你
Some people just want to use you
满足他们愚蠢的欲望
for their own stupid desires
自私的目的 甚至是琐碎的争吵
or selfish aims or petty squabbles.
他们都懒得把你当人看
They don't even bother seeing you as a human being.
不管你俩发生了什么
I don't know what's going on between the two of you,
我都不想参与其中
but I don't want any part of it.
我要讲自己的故事
I'm gonna tell my own story.
感谢您的时间
- Well, thank you for your time.
-祝你顺利 旺达  -感谢
- You have a great day, Wanda. - Thank you.
-开心了吧  -够了
- Happy? - Oh, my God.
欢迎来到
Welcome back to day five
“男人站起来”行动的第五天
of the M.E.N. offensive.
我们好像戳到痛处了 各位
Now, we've struck a nerve, folks.
收听率高得惊人
Ratings are through the roof.
我都在重新跟电台谈合同了
Contracts are being renegotiated.
我买个带游泳池的家
I'm getting an in-ground pool,
不许你来用 老妈
and you can't come use it, Ma.
在威利的法律行动之外
Now, in addition to Willy's legal action,
我们还会为那些
we'll be providing resources
不知如何提起诉讼的人提供帮助
to men who can't file lawsuits of their own.
冲突正式升级了 朋友们
That's called an escalation of conflict, my friends.
你猜怎么着
And guess what.
女士们也想分一杯羹
The ladies want a piece of the action, too,
今天我们请到了一位优秀的
and we have the most impressive lady of all
一位女嘉宾
here with us today.
南加州第一位
The first female councilman
女议员
in Southern California
一位大美人
and a total babe to boot.
圣费尔南多谷的骄傲
The pride of the San Fernando Valley,
布里吉特·韦斯特伯里
Bridget Westbury.
很高兴来到这里
- Well, it's a pleasure to be here.
发生在 你们同伴身上的事
What happened to your... person
这场十足的闹剧 我们都知道该怪谁
is a travesty, and we all know who's responsible.
我怪“莫德”“玛丽·泰勒·摩尔”
I blame "Maude," "Mary Tyler Moore,"
以及“那个女孩”
and to a lesser extent, "That Girl."
都是我们的敌人
- Mm, enemies all.
但我们要向他们宣战
But we're taking the fight to them.
大家一直以来都投票反对核电站
People vote all the time to ban nuclear power plants
反对露天矿
and strip mines,
这些振兴我们经济的产业
and those industries make our economy strong.
而恰恰是像《风骚女子》这样的色情杂志削弱了我们的社区
Pornography like "Minx" enfeebles our community.
因此 我要在周一提出决议
That's why on Monday, I'm proposing a resolution
圣费尔南多山谷
to ban the production of pornographic materials
全面禁止色情产业
in the San Fernando Valley.
果然激进
Bold move.
作为一个 不
Let me say, as someone who does not
喜欢色情作品的人 我要说
find pornography appealing...
把这些肮脏玩意儿
Let's leave the filth
送给下流的欧洲人吧
to the dirty Europeans.
加州人是开拓先驱
Californians have always been pioneers,
我很骄傲 能驾着这辆马车
and I am proud to lead the wagon
创造更干净更美好的山谷
into my valley... cleaner and nicer.
我都能闻见了
I can almost smell it.
-人都去哪儿了  -我让他们回家了
- Where is everybody? - I sent them home.
很好 外面的氛围很怪
Good, it's weird vibes out there.
我看到一人尿了自己一身 而且毫不介意
I saw a guy piss on himself and not seem to mind.
警察呢
Oh. - What about the cops?
我报过警 但这是白人的和平抗议
- I called, but it's a peaceful protest of white men,
他们可是出了名的冷静理智
a famously calm, reasonable people.
好吧 得让他们走人
Okay. All right, we gotta get them out of there.
-我有个主意  -是吧 放手去做
- I have an idea. - Yeah? Do that.
2天内增加了13起诉讼 据说
13 more lawsuits in two days, and word on the street:
后续还有十几个
dozens more on the way.
朋友们 你们深陷其中了
You are in it now, my friends.
这种案子很偏激
They're outlandish.
任何一位有声望的律师都不会
I mean, surely no reputable lawyer will--
创造激动人心的判例
What, wanna create an exciting new legal precedent
流芳教科书吗
and be in textbooks forever?
亲 这是我的人生梦想啊
Doll, my kind lives for this shit.
这个色情禁令 是认真的吗
This porn ban, is it real?
维斯伯理是个投机倒把的
· Well, Westbury is an opportunistic SOB
混蛋还是婊子吧
or DOB or whatever.
尼克松要连任了
Nixon's about to be reelected.
提醒一下 60年代结束了
News flash: the '60s are over.
这个应该能帮我们搞定
- Well, I think this will help us take care
女议员的
of the councilwoman, so...
是吗 我看看
- Huh? Okay.
我天 不错啊
Oh, that's fascinating.
太好了
That's great.
你去挖女议员的黑料了
You've got dirt on the councilwoman?
对 未雨稠缪了
Yeah, I was saving it for a rainy day.
她的虚伪令人震惊
The hypocrisy is staggering.
终于有抄近路的办法了
I mean, taking the high road--
你干嘛啊
What are you doing?
你在干什么
- What are you doing?
勒索政府官员是重罪
It's a felony to blackmail a government employee
我知道了可能会丢了律师执照的
and disbarment for me to even know about it.
你得有多傻 才会把这东西交我手上
What kind of shmendrik hands this to his lawyer?
拜托 迈伦 我们肯定有对策的
- All right, Myron, come on. There's always a move.
有 暂停《风骚女人》吧
Yeah, there is. Fold "Minx."
也别想着发布第三期的事儿
Don't even think about publishing the third issue.
今日新闻 明日黄花 案子风头也会过去
The news cycle moves on. Lawsuits fade away.
他们只是想让你难堪 道格
They're just trying to jam you up, Dougie,
但你可别上当啊
but don't take the bait.
你还有自己的公司
You still have your company,
你的头衔也不只这一个
and you can hold on to your other titles.
而你 你可以利用这次狼藉名声
And you, you can use the notoriety
再打下一个江山
to start something new.
听着 好的一面
Okay, look, the bright side?
从我的角度看你俩
From what I've seen of the two of you,
不是所有的搭档永远都不会分开
not all partnerships are meant to last.
也许分开是件好事
Maybe it's a good thing
你俩也不用再一起工作了
that you two don't have to work together anymore.
我们想要什么
What do we want?
抵制底袋钱
多一些小妹妹
少一些小弟弟
让男人不受女人威胁
For men to be safe from women!
我们什么时候要
And when do we want it?
让乔伊斯禁言
昨天
all: Yesterday!
驯服 《风骚女人》
Tame the "Minx"!
all: Tame the "Minx"!
驯服风骚女人 驯服风骚女人
Tame the "Minx"! Tame the "Minx"!
我们得想办法脱身 你得帮助我们
- We're gonna get out of it, and you're gonna help us.
没问题 没问题 想要什么
- All right, all right. Anything I can do...
-我知道  -尽管开口
- I know. - You just call me.
-你一直都是如此  -好了
- You've always been-- - All right.
-让我跟他们聊聊  -这就是你的主意
- Let me talk to those guys. - This is your idea?
-你有什么更好的主意吗  -我可以把他们赶走
- You got something better? - I can get them to leave.
你肯定不行 他们就是一群疯子
No, you can't. They're lunatics.
我一直都在强调这一点
That's what I've been saying,
但有的人这几天就是很鲁莽
but someone's being very reckless these days.
好吧 我跟你一起去
Okay, well, I'll come with you.
不
No.
我强而有力
I am a vessel of power.
所有这些人都迷恋我
All of these men fantasize about me,
我言一出
and when I speak,
他们必定听我号令
they will obey my every command.
这就是我试镜《埃及艳后》的台词
That was for my audition for Cleopatra.
我不明白啥意思
I didn't get it.
你拉一下试试 小斑
Try pulling, Bam.
我们要这么做吗
We're doing this?
也可能有用
It might work.
金博 诺曼
Jimbo, Norman.
臭皮特 他们这么早就放你出来了
Stinky Pete, they let you out early.
-是啊  -我们爱你 斑比
- Yeah. - We love you, Bambi.
我也爱你们
I love you too.
兄弟们
Boys...
世界变化不停
the world is changing.
我知道很多人并不像以往一样去看待事物
I know a lot of people don't look or think
去思考事情 这是会让人感到不安
the way they used to and that can be scary,
但我们并不软弱
but we're strong.
我们心理强大 团结起来
We have big hearts, and together
一起面对这个世界
we can face this world,
一切都会好的
and it's gonna be okay.
是啊
Yeah.
没必要生气
There's no need for anger here.
《风骚女人》不是你们的敌人
"Minx" isn't your enemy.
她是一个特殊的存在
It's a special place
可以让我以崭新的眼光看待新事物
that's opened my eyes to so many new things.
在这里 我的想法同样重要 我也有权发声
Here, my ideas matter, and I have a voice.
我 来自瑞西达途经吉隆坡的卢安·普里兹比尔科
Me, Luann Pryzbylko from Reseda by way of Kuala Lumpur.
现在正是时候给你们分享这些消息
And it's high time I shared some news with you,
因为你们不只是我的粉丝
because you're not just my fans.
你们是我的家人
You're my family.
就像一只喇叭天鹅
Like the trumpeter swan,
她脱去稚嫩的羽翼
she's shed her juvenile feathers
将在夺目的白色光晕重新示人
and reemerged in a blinding white blaze of beauty.
我他妈得赶紧走了
I need to get the fuck out of here.
我犯了个错误
I made a mistake.
我以为分享真相是打动他们的最有效的方式
I thought sharing my truth was the surest way to their hearts,
所以我告诉他们 我将正式告别裸体模特界
so I told them I officially retired from nude modeling.
还正式
Aw, officially?
我的天啊
Oh, Jesus, God.
他们还以为你把我给洗脑了
Yeah, they think you brainwashed me,
他们很生气
and they're very angry.
完了 他们已经突破了防线
Oh, they've breached the perimeter.
后退
Okay, fall back.
-后退  -去哪儿
- Fall back! - To where?
-什么  -排版室
- What? - The layout room.
我们会被困住 但这也是最好的掩护
We'll be pinned down, but it provides the best cover.
-你怎么知道  -我来自军人家庭
- How do you know that? - Military family.
行了 你们认真的吗
Come on. Are we really doing this?
把那扇窗户封起来
Let's get that window boarded up.
我移一下沙发 借过一下
Okay, I'm moving the couch. Excuse me.
乔伊斯 信件包
Joyce, mailbags.
好的
Yeah.
我们真的要躲着这些白痴吗
Are we really hiding from these jelly doughnuts?
我们真要这么做吗
That's what we're doing right now?
底袋钱 被他自己的粉丝给攻击了
Bottom Dollar attacked by its own fans.
在我看来就是个极好的的宣传噱头
Sounds like an A-plus publicity stunt to me.
这些处男怎么这么暴躁啊
Who knew virgins could be so mean?
远离窗户 斑比
- Get away from the window, Bambi.
他们正在找你
They're looking for you.
蒂娜 把灯关了
- Tina, kill the lights.
陛下
Your Majesty...
是时候叫点人出来了
time to call a minion.
底袋钱 外面情况已经失控了
Things have gotten out of hand down at Bottom Dollar.
我们应该送些警察过去
We should send a couple black-and-whites.
我觉得还是再等等看事情发展如何
Or wait and see how the situation unfolds.
不要太草率
Don't wanna be too hasty.
警察不来的
- Cops aren't coming.
维斯伯里要让我们自生自灭
Westbury's hanging us out to dry on this.
太熟悉了
Settle in.
我觉得我要死这儿了
Well, I guess I'll die right here
比利的雪橇
紧挨着我的最大的耻辱
next to my greatest humiliation.
真是凤头豹尾啊
Perfect end to a perfect chapter.
没人会死
Oh, nobody's gonna die.
他们只是要发泄一下 仅此而已
They're just blowing off some steam, that's all.
我们肯定还有能联系的人
Oh, there must be someone we can call.
那些为比利·布伦森而疯狂的暴徒呢
What about those goons this one trotted out for Billy Brunson?
你想要这里血流成河吗
Oh, what, you wanna turn this into a bloodbath?
总比咱们流血强吧
Better their blood than ours.
那个知道黑帮给她运杂志后
- What happened to the Joyce who had an aneurysm
差点晕过去的乔伊斯呢
when she found out the Mob was delivering her magazine?
因为遇见了你
You happened to me.
这锁着的
Hey, this one's locked.
诺曼找到了雷内蒂的办公室
Norman found Renetti's office.
走
Come on.
我去 真不错
- Whoa. All right, come on!
这些畜生要是敢动我的相机
If those animals get into my cameras,
我不打死他们才怪
I swear I'll fight them myself.
好了 听着 不用担心你的设备
All right, listen, don't worry about the gear.
等一切都结束了
When this is all over,
你想要什么我给你买什么 好吗
I'll buy anything you want, okay?
你为什么要给我的摄影师
· Why would you buy new equipment
买新设备
for my photographer?
我想给我新任的艺术总监
I can buy anything I want
买什么买什么
for my new art director.
是吧 朋友
Right, pal?
感谢你的好意
Yeah, I appreciate your interest,
还是不了 谢谢你
but no, thank you.
我明白了 这一切在你看来都是游戏吗
- Oh, I see. So all that was game to you?
不 这不是游戏 道格
No, it's not a game, Doug.
这只是被霸凌感觉的
It's just a small taste of what it's like
冰山一角
to be pushed around by a bully.
不过还是要谢谢你的谈判大师课
But thank you for your master class in negotiation.
这些读者来信
These reader letters.
他们爱我们
People love us.
除了你
Well, not you.
我所做的一切 都是为了底袋钱
- Well, everything I did, I did for Bottom Dollar.
看看这个
Look at that.
他把我的信放到了正中间
He put me front and center.
你的高光时刻啊
It's your time to shine.
你的杂志让我开心
- "Your magazine made me feel good
追求内心所爱 也让我对那些阻止我的人
"about wanting what I want and angry at people
感到生气
"trying to stop me from getting it.
在这个不公且美好的世界里
"'Minx' is a refuge for every woman
风骚女人 是每个感到孤独的女人的避难所
who thinks she's alone in this wicked, wonderful world."
每一个人都因为我们站了出来
Each one of these is a person reaching out because of us.
这个孩子问我们有没有实习
This kid is asking if we have any internships.
他才16岁
He's 16 years old.
他把中间插页放在床垫下面
Ah, he keeps the centerfold under his mattress.
我们得帮这孩子离开密西西比
Ooh, we gotta get this boy the hell out of Mississippi.
我的天啊 这个女人邀请我们去她的婚礼
- My, God, this woman is inviting us to her wedding.
这只是沙拉的收据
- This is just a recipe for a Tuscan bread salad.
信在这儿
Oh, there it is.
还有人给孩子取名乔伊斯
Someone named their baby Joyce.
我的天啊
- Oh. Oh, my God.
还附了张可乐罐作为参考
There's a soda can as a reference point.
她接受了她老公
- Oh, she took her husband back...
带他去了精神病院
to the asylum.
什么味儿啊
What is that smell?
-我的天啊  -好了 到此为止了
- Oh, my God. - All right, that's it.
这他妈不能再这样了 叫那群俄罗斯过来吧
This fucking ends now. Let's call the Russians.
-已经打了  -谢了
- Already did. - Thank you.
没了你我该怎么办啊
What would I do without you?
杜克大学
加州大学伯克利分校
沃顿商学院
芝加哥大学 工商管理学院
亲爱的蒂娜·露易丝，
我谨代表芝加哥大学，很高兴通知您您已
被我校1973年秋季招生计划录取
随信附上登记表 填写并于1972年12月12日前寄回
请及时回复以便您于我校安排住宿事宜
山谷之王躲到了帕萨迪纳
- King of the valley found his way to Pasadena.
我又不反感长途开车
- Well, I don't hate a road trip.
我还去了玫瑰碗 还拍了照
I even went to the Rose Bowl. I took a picture.
你看《贝琪》了吗
You see "Betsy"?
温迪真的把我们写惨了啊
Wendy really did a number on us, huh?
对 她把我描绘
Yeah, I got off easy
成自命不凡的唯我论者
with "pretentious" and "solipsistic."
而你 是个油腻的P.T. 巴纳姆和犹太人的混合体
You are "a greasy P.T. Barnum with a dash of"
看来她文笔还不错
Maybe I misjudged her as a writer.
她有理由生气
She had good reason to be pissed.
我们原本说好了的 可最后关头我叫停了
We had a deal, and I pulled the plug at the last minute.
她开销太大了
Her taste too rich for your blood?
不是钱的事儿
No, it wasn't about the money.
我只是觉得她不适合 风骚女人
I just didn't think she was the right fit for "Minx."
为什么 我觉得她完美契合啊
Why? Seems like a match made in heaven.
那她也不是你啊
Because she's not you.
是这样 你做创造的东西 对人们是有意义的
Look, what you made, it means something to people,
我却不知道怎么办
and I didn't know what to do with that.
所以我把它搞得面目全非
And so I turned it into something pretty ugly,
我自己
and I got--
我自己也一直是一团糟
I got pretty ugly along the way, too, so...
能承认这一点说明你很大度
That is very big of you to admit.
我知道我们这一次是在逆风而行
And I know that we're sailing against the wind on this one,
做成什么样是我的原因 但我可以扭转局势
and I'm responsible for that, but I can fix this.
这次我们作为搭档一起扭转局势
We can fix this together as partners this time
谁敢挡路干死他丫的
and fuck everybody who's trying to stop us.
上周我接了个电话
You know, I got a call last week
不知道哪儿冒出来的一个经纪人打的
from a literally agent just out of the blue
告诉我机会遍地都是
telling me about all the opportunities out there
我可以
and that it's just a matter of me
随意决定想做什么
deciding what I wanna do next.
挺好的 你是值得的
- Oh, good. You've earned that.
是啊 不过
Yeah, but...
不过所有这些机会后面
attached to each one of those opportunities
都有一个道格·雷内蒂
is another Doug Renetti,
有人有求于我
someone who wants something from me,
他们永远都做不到事
something that they could never do on their own
但他们还是想掌控全局
but still insists on holding all the power.
我再也不想放弃自己的权力了
I'm not sure I'm interested in giving away my power anymore.
所以就这了 你想一个人去做
So that's it? You're gonna go at it alone?
也许吧
Maybe.
出了两期杂志你就敢当出版商了
Two issues and you're ready to be a publisher?
你胆子也太大了
I mean, the stones on you.
这么说吧
I'll tell you what.
《风骚女人》是你的
"Minx" is yours.
没有你我也不想干下去 给你吧
Yeah, I don't wanna do it without you, so take it.
带着它遨游世界吧
Go to all the places you wanna go with it.
我等不及要看你有所成就
I can't wait to see what you do.
道格
- Doug.
谢谢你
Thank you.
祝你好运
Good luck.